

Front End Developer Graphic Designer



A creative and technical individual looking to transition into a Web Development role. With 1 year of experience in building web applications as well as over 5 years experience with Graphic Design. I aim to leverage my knowledge in prototyping and user experience to solve creative problems and build applications for the internet.

Work Experience

UI/UX Designer - Mixr Online Inc.

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021 (Contract) London, ON

- Developed layouts and prototypes demonstrating app functionality and user flow.
- Produced themes and other reusable assets for the Mixr application.
- Created graphics for product concepts, sales presentations, & https://mixronline.com/
- Implemented a re-design of the Mixr logo and developed the Mixr branding guidelines

Marketing Coordinator - Ingersoll Products Inc.

May 2019 - Apr 2020 (Full Time) *Ingersoll, ON*

- Generated omni-channel marketing campaigns utilizing Facebook, Google, Amazon, & email.
- Developed & re-designed existing website using the commerce platform Squarespace.
- Assessed analytics from advertising efforts to optimize campaigns & align sales targets.
- Oversaw implementation & design of new product packaging from concept to creation.

Freelance Graphic & Web Designer

Sept 2017 - June 2020

- Designed and launched websites using platforms like Squarespace and Wordpress.
- Provided consulting on branding, advertising, & design strategies for small businesses.
- Established contracts relating to farming, manufacturing, real estate development, & more.

Education

Interactive Media Design Sept 2020 - Apr 2022 Fanshawe College

• Dean's Honour Roll

Graphic Design

Sept 2015 - Apr 2018 **Fanshawe College**

Volunteer Experience Web Designer

Jan 2022 - Present

OCNVA - Woodstock, ON

Content Producer
Sept 2020 - Apr 2021
Young London (LYAC)

Graphic Designer
May 2017 - Jan 2019
OCNVA - Woodstock, ON

Skills

HTML & CSS, JAVASCRIPT, VUE.JS, NODE.JS, NPM, JSON, PHP, SQL, SASS, GULP, HEROKU Creativity, Adaptability, Problem solving, Hard working

mindofjacob.ca

linkedin.com/in/mindofjacob/